You
She really is Sylphie
How did I not recognize her?
I guess my impression of Fitz was just too different, or maybe it's just that she grew up
She was really attached to me back in the day and always wanted me around
While Fitz is much more independent and reliable
But she can still be kind of an airhead too
That shy smile of hers makes my heart swell every time and she's telling me she loves me
If I don't tell her how I feel right now, I could lose her again. I don't want any more regrets like that
Sylphie, I
Won't go. I love you
Oh
I
I'm sorry, Sylphie. I've been this way for three years. I think it's a psychological illness.
Rudy.
Embarrassing you was the last thing I wanted to do. I'm so sorry.
Rudy, stop. I'm not embarrassed about anything, okay? Go back to normal.
As much as I would love to return to normal, I don't think I can.
That's not what I mean. Just stop being so formal.
Oh, right. I'm sorry. I'm getting kind of flustered.
No more fancy talk from now on, okay?
As you wish.
You're still doing it.
That one's not so bad, is it?
Thank you for this pendant, by the way.
I'm glad it got to you. I always assumed it was long gone.
Lilia held onto it for us.
That's sweet.
So anyway, why do you disguise yourself as a boy?
Right, all of that. I don't even know where to start.
Well, I watched you being taken away in the carriage that day. You were unconscious. I was so shocked that I attacked Paul.
Really? You?
I mean, it was really sudden. And I was confused and angry. But that day, I promised myself that I'd get strong enough to save you.
My mind was made up.
I started studying. I practiced magic. I even asked Lilia to teach me some etiquette.
I just wanted to catch up to you. I wanted to be worthy. I worked so hard.
Then came the mass teleportation. It warped me to the royal palace, where I met Princess Ariel and Luke.
What happened between then and university is kind of a long story.
But I was so glad when I saw your name on a list of potential new students.
Thank you for being alive.
You're welcome.
And thank you, too.
And I get why, but it was so weird to hear you introduce yourself to me like a stranger.
I bet. I'm sorry. I just can't believe you didn't say something sooner.
I guess I should have. I just couldn't work up the courage. Sorry.
That's okay. If I weren't so oblivious, you wouldn't have had to.
Ah! Rudy, you can't do that in public.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
So I do get some response. I just can't control it.
But progress is progress.
And now I can safely say I'm on the mend.
All thanks to her.
What are you staring at?
Well, I've got business with the Princess, so I should go.
Okay.
And I guess...
We'll see each other soon?
Oh, right.
Yes.
Uh, guess so.
Or I would like that very much anyway.
I wish I had some kind of medicine for Rudy's condition.
So you failed, I take it?
Well, no. I wouldn't say that.
And was a bad plan in hindsight.
Even if there was a risk of freezing,
I suppose it's expecting a lot of someone
to tear the clothing off a friend like that.
Sylphie, just tell us exactly what happened, please.
Um, okay.
You can't be serious.
Huh?
No, that's why he's at the university.
He's looking for a way to cure his impotence.
Just imagine.
To be so useless in the one moment it really counts.
Goodness, I may have rather overestimated this rudious fellow.
I don't think you're being fair.
Huh?
There are times when a man can't help it.
It's not as though Rudy has spurned her
or failed to make love to her by choice.
In fact, this could explain why he's been so hesitant.
He's afraid to disappoint.
Sure.
I've always wondered why he looked so insecure.
So meek and withdrawn.
That poor fellow.
He must have come here out of sheer desperation
with nowhere else to turn for help.
I beg your pardon then.
It would appear I spoke too strongly.
That's all right.
It's only natural that your highness wouldn't understand.
Sylphie, how do you feel about all this
and would you want to help cure him?
Uh, uh, mm-hmm.
He's been taking the entire situation to heart.
So yeah, of course I want to do what I can for him.
But are you committed to knowing
that it may prove to be a challenge?
Yes.
I'll do anything.
All right then.
I may have something for you.
I'll have to go get it.
Your highness, excuse me.
Again, I do hope you can forgive me.
I misspoke about Rudeus.
It's fine.
I'm not upset.
Well, Luke obviously has some kind of plan
he'd like to set in motion.
But as it happens,
I actually know several cures for impotence myself.
Really?
What are they?
Okay.
What are you doing?
I am returning to where I began
and practicing incantationless magic.
Then keep it down.
Give me practice that part of it more.
Go, Master Sanobo!
Getting them drunk first,
you should be like...
I'm back.
Thanks for waiting.
...alcohol.
Of course.
But then you suddenly notice how hot it is.
Bare your shoulders a little and voila.
And you think that's enough to do it?
Oh, there's no doubt in my mind.
You have the perfect look to pull that off.
All you need is opportunity.
And perhaps a few choice words
prepared to seal the deal.
No.
Complaining of heat in the dead of winter like that
would get you taken to a medic.
But in any season,
Sophie doesn't have the figure for feminine wiles.
You needn't put it so brutishly, Luke.
Your Highness, the gray rat men
have been drawn to buck some women for generations.
If he's anything like the rest of us,
it won't work.
Personally, I feel no attraction to Sophie at all
and I never have.
However...
Wow, what is that for?
This lady's is a powerful Fitoan aphrodisiac.
Behold.
You're joking.
It was at one time
widely distributed,
but the facility where it was manufactured
and the recipe they used
were lost to the mass teleportation,
so eventually,
the asking price soared
to over 100 gold pieces per bottle.
I've been holding on to this
in case I ever found myself
in urgent need of money.
But...
you should take it.
It's so valuable, though.
Are you sure?
Of course.
But listen,
any man who drinks this stuff
will completely lose control.
So if you can't keep up,
you may want to drink some of it yourself.
And keep in mind that your first time
won't go the way you've envisioned.
It never does.
Thank you, Luke.
I appreciate it.
Oh, think nothing of it.
You've saved my life often enough.
I definitely owed you.
I love how you two have become friends.
Here, let me chip in, too.
But, Princess,
isn't this your personal money?
Yes, my spending money for this month.
Please take it.
At this point in the game,
it's the only helpful thing
I have left to give.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Benevolent is always your grace.
Sylvie.
Best of luck.
Okay.
Here I go.
Princess Ariel picked out
some new underwear for me.
And I have the aphrodisiac
that Luke gave me.
Okay.
Mom, Dad,
give me your blessing.
Tonight,
I'm going to become a woman.
Yes?
Oh, hey,
Syl...
Master Fitz, rather.
Please,
come on in.
Thanks.
So, what's up?
You were so tired earlier.
I thought you'd be going straight to bed.
Well,
I came to stay the night.
Huh?
Oh.
Okay.
If you want,
come in and sit down, then.
What is that?
Oh,
I brought that for us to share.
After all,
we ought to do something
to celebrate our reunion,
right?
Oh.
Yeah, true.
We should commemorate the occasion.
Here.
You need cups, right?
I have plenty.
I eat in here a lot.
Well then,
here's to old friends
from Buena Village
reunited at last.
Cheers.
And to our future,
Sylphie.
Yeah,
cheers.
Our future?
Rudy says the most embarrassing stuff sometimes.
That's no good.
Are you okay?
You did get some awfully strong stuff.
Let me see it.
Huh?
Here.
I'll dilute it.
This would probably be pretty good with hot water.
Now try it.
Ah,
thank you.
You know what's funny?
That hot water trick
is why I started learning magic from you.
Oh,
was it really?
Remember?
Those bullies have been pelting me with mud.
So you helped me rinse off
on this side of the road.
Oh, yeah.
That was so long ago.
Yeah.
I wonder if our tree is still there
in Buena Village.
I was thinking about it a lot
on our walk through the forest.
Yeah,
we did spend a lot of time
under that tree, huh?
That's where we had
all of our magic lessons.
You showed me
how to conjure water first.
And silent spellcasting
came so naturally to you.
It did, yeah.
That was a lot of fun.
I forgot.
I brought something else, too.
What is that?
It's a medicine
that's supposed to fix
your you-know-what.
I don't know
if it's medicine exactly,
but it is a drug,
so I don't think I'm lying.
I think I've seen this
somewhere before.
Uh,
I was hoping
you'd give it a try.
It's supposed to work right away
from what I hear.
Hang on.
Do you know
if it's safe
to take this with alcohol?
Yeah,
they said it's fine
to mix them,
I think.
And once it kicks in,
you don't have to hold back,
okay?
Okay?
Okay.
Do you want
to try some, too?
Are you okay?
I'm just a little nervous.
Right.
Yeah.
Me, too.
Sylphiette.
You can't resist anymore.
Hm.
Then go ahead.
I want you to devour me, Rudy.
Oh, I remember.
That was the aphrodisiac the peddler in Roa was hawking, huh?
She has guard duty today.
She'll come back.
Oh, good.
You're awake.
Hi, Rudy.
Good morning.
Sorry I left.
I just went to thank Princess Ariel and Luke for all their help yesterday.
Or, I mean, for giving me the push I needed.
Well, anyway, they were both overjoyed.
You should come with me to see them sometime.
I think the princess...
What's the matter?
Sylvie.
My Sylvie.
Silly Rudy.
Don't cry.
I'm right here.
Really, Rudy?
Don't cry.
I'm right here.
Rudy, excuse you.
Thank you, Sylphée.
Thank you. I love you.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Rudeus Greyrat at your service.
Your reputation resounds throughout this school like a thunderclap.
What brings you here to see me today, Rudeus?
I imagine that Sylphée… Sylphiette, rather, has told you most everything.
But there's one thing I wanted to say in person.
Your Highness, Sylphée was so good as to cure my condition.
And I'm given to understand that you and Master Luke helped her to do so.
Therefore, if I can ever be of service to you, you only need but ask.
Generous.
But I thought that you shied away from power struggles between Osir and nobles.
True enough.
I'd rather not stick my nose into a political dispute.
However, if my beloved is caught up in one, that changes things.
I would be extremely glad of your support. You're a valuable ally.
Now then, what's next for you, Rudeus?
Personally, I have a duty to find family members lost in the mass teleportation.
In which case, I won't be able to set out for Asura immediately.
Oh goodness, of course.
My affairs can wait until after you've resolved your own.
But what will that mean for you and Sylphée, then?
Sorry?
Oh, come now.
Don't tell me that now that you've cured your impotence, you'll simply journey forth.
Yes, you have a duty to your family.
But will you bid Sylphée goodbye?
Of course I won't. I want to marry her.
Sylphée at Greyrat.
Sylphée Greyrat?
Surely you have some response to that.
To marriage? I don't know.
Ah!
Luke!
Well, I guess...
I mean...
What I want to say...
Y-yes?
Rudy...
Please take good care of me.
Of course.
Always.
Sylphée, if you're going to become Rudy's wife,
I should stop asking you to dress like a man.
You may dress as you wish.
But Princess...
And as for you,
I intend to make good use of your reputation in my sphere of influence.
Please don't shy away from using my name and kind.
Understood.
Your Highness...
Master Luke...
Thank you for everything.
Hehe.
Your Highness...
Master Luke...
Thank you for everything.
Hehe.
Thank you.